Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1991-2010; 7
  - 111th Congress, 2009-2010; 10
    - Appropriations, Energy & Water Development, 2009 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Energy & Water Development, Oversight and Member Requests, 2009 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Financial Services & General Government 2010, 2009 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Ft. Carson, Colorado, 2010 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Homeland Security, 2009 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Housing & Urban Development 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Houston Ship Channel Certification Letters FY 11, 2010 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, Interior Certification Letters FY 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Interior Environment 2010, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Labor, Health & Human Services & Education, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Legislative Branch 2010, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Medical Treatment Facilities Master Plan FY 09, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, American battle Monuments Commission FY 11, 2010 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, FY10, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, Hospitals, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, Part 7, 2009 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction and Veterans Affairs, 2009 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Military Construction, Veterans Affairs FY 11/Full Committee Markup, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Military Family Housing, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, New Gymnasium at Liberty Intermediate School, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Revised Suballocation of Budget Allocations for FY 2010, 2009 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, School Facilities Serving Gaining Installations, 2009 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Supplemental Appropriations, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, Training Operations for Urban Operations, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, Transportation, “TIGER”, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations, Transportation, “TIGER” II, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, TX Requests FY2009 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations, TX Requests FY10 (1 of 3), 2009 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, TX Requests FY10 (2 of 3), 2009 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, TX Requests FY10 (3 of 3), 2009 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Transportation, Housing & Urban Development 2011, 2010 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs, General, 2009-2010 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs Budget Submissions FY 11 (1 of 4), 2010 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs Budget Submissions FY 11 (2 of 4), 2010 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs Budget Submissions FY 11 (3 of 4), 2010 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs Budget Submissions FY 11 (4 of 4), 2010 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs, Hearing, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Veterans Affairs, Medical Care FY 11, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Armed Forces, 235th Birthday, United States Army, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Armed Forces, Air Force, MC-12W Project Liberty Enterprise Team, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Armed Forces, Army, 2009-2010 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Armed Forces, Children’s School Investment Act, HR 2593, 2009-2010 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Armed Forces, Davis-Bacon Act, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Armed Forces, Defense, Threat Reduction Agency, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Armed Forces, Employment, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Armed Forces, Exercise Related Construction Program, 2010 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Armed Forces, Family Housing-Navy, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Armed Forces, Family of Medium Tactical Vehicles (FMTV), 2009 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Armed Forces, Fort Hood, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Armed Forces, Fort Hood, HR 319, Shooting Anniversary, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Armed Forces, Guam, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Armed Forces, Institute of Medicine (IOM), 2010 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Armed Forces, Iraqi Base Closure Report, 2009-2010 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Armed Forces, Marine Expeditionary Brigade, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Armed Forces, Military Construction Projects, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Armed Forces, Military, Quality of Life, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Armed Forces, National Defense Authorization Act FY 91, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Armed Forces, Patient Evacuation Vehicles (PEV’s), 2009 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Armed Forces, Small Business Program, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Armed Forces, Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI), 2010 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Armed Forces, Undergraduate Nurse Training Program, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Budget, Budget Conference FY 10, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Budget, Congressionally Directed Spending Items FY 10, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Budget, Economic Outlook FY '10-'20, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Budget, House Committee Members, 2009-2010 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Budget, State of Economy, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Budget, TX Requests, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Commemoratives, Dr. John Hope Franklin, HR 320, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Commemoratives, Dr. Norman E. Borlaug, HR 183, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Economy, American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - Economy, FDIC, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Economy, Job Impact by Districts, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Economy, Jobs, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Economy, Mailing, Undated (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Economy, Recovery Act Next Steps, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Economy, Recovery Benefits to Districts, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Economy, Recovery Through Tax Cuts, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Economy, Reinvestment Act, Child Support Funding, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Economy, Reinvestment Act, Emergency Shelter Funds, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Economy, Reinvestment Act, State Unemployment Insurance Help, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - Economy, Sample Stimulus Events Memo, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Economy, Securities and Exchanges Commission, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - Economy, Speaker Pelosi on Republican Plan, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 37)
    - Economy, Speaker Pelosi’s Office on Recovery, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 38)
    - Education, Budget Summary, Dept. of Education, 2010 (Box 146, Folder 39)
    - Education, Secondary Education Act of 1965, HR 2593, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 40)
    - Education, Student Loans, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 41)
    - Energy, Advanced Energy Manufacturing Tax Credit, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - Environment, Central Texas Water Recycling Act Draft, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 43)
    - Environment, Central Texas Water Recycling HR 1120, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 44)
    - Financial Services, Capital One, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 45)
    - Financial Services, Citi, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 46)
    - Financial Services, Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 47)
    - Financial Services, Limit Executive Compensation Abuse Act, HR 857, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 48)
    - Financial Services, Small Business Opportunity Act, HR 2281, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 49)
    - Financial Services, Taxpayer Repayment Act, HR 2832, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 50)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Congress Pay Adjustment, HR 156, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 51)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Constitution: Jefferson’s Manual and Rules of the House of Representatives, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, House Army Caucus Registration Amendment, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Kyle G. West Post Office Building, HR 2422, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Government Affairs/House Administration, Review of Federal Agencies, HR 393, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Health, General, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Health, American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Health, Cancer Prevention, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Health, Disease Outbreaks, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Health, H1N1 Influenza Virus, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Health, Health Care Reform, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Health, Hospital Financial Pressures, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Health, Medicare, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Health, Physician Practice Expense Information Survey (PPIS), 2009 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Health, Reproductive Rights, 2009-2010 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Health, Scott & White, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Health, Seniors, Mailing, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Health, Skilled Nursing Facility Care, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Health, Texas Medicaid, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Health, Tobacco, Production Regulation, HR 1256, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Health, Tourette Syndrome, 2010 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Homeland Security, Border Reinforcement, HR 1448, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Homeland Security, Budget in Brief, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Homeland Security, Edwards on Border Security, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Homeland Security, Guantanamo Votes, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Interior, Waco Mammoth Site, HR 1376, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary and Law Enforcement, Alvarado Police Department Community Oriented Policing Services Grant, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary and Law Enforcement, Bureau of Prisons Short Term Sentence, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Judiciary and Law Enforcement, Condemning the Murder of Dr. George Tiller, HR 505, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary and Law Enforcement, Local Radio Freedom Act, HR 49, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Airlines Anti-Trust, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Air Traffic-Collegiate Training Initiative (AT-CTI), 2009 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, High-Speed Intercity Passenger Rail (HSIPR), 2010 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Infrastructure, Albert Armendariz, Sr. United States Courthouse, HR 2053, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Southeast Vocational Alliance, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Tower 55 Rail Intersection Upgrade Project, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Veterans, Alcohol Dependence, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Veterans, Arlington National Cemetery Budget Justification, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Veterans, Budget FY 2010, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Veterans, East Tennessee State Veterans Cemetery Grant, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Veterans, Mailing, “Historic Commitment to America’s Veterans”, undated (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Veterans, Mailing, “Honoring America’s Military Families & Veterans”, undated (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Veterans, Pointe du Hoc, 2009-2010 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Veterans, State of Colorado Grant, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Veterans, State of Maine Grant, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Veterans, State of Ohio Grants, 2009-2010 (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, State of Oklahoma Grant, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - Veterans, Suicide Prevention Program, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - Veterans, Women Air Force Service Pilots (WASP), 2009 (Box 148, Folder 28)
- Press, 1991-2008; 8
  All press-related files generated by Edwards’ office are organized into by type: Columns, Mailers, News Releases, Newsletters, and Radio Calls. Materials are categorized as general for their broad scope and organized chronologically. Newsletters contains documents addressed to Edwards’ constituents and are organized by topic. These letters deal with issues relevant to the congressman’s district.
  - Columns, 1991-1992; 1
    - General, 1991-1992 (Box 148, Folder 29)
    - General, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 30)
    - General, 1995 (Box 148, Folder 31)
    - General, 1996 (Box 148, Folder 32)
    - General, 1997 (Box 148, Folder 33)
    - General, 1998 (Box 148, Folder 34)
    - General, 1999 (Box 148, Folder 35)
    - General, 2000 (Box 148, Folder 36)
    - General, 2001 (Box 148, Folder 37)
    - General, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 38)
  - Mailers, 2004-2008; 2
    - Town Halls, 2004 July (Box 148, Folder 39)
    - Homeland Security, 2004 July 4 (Box 148, Folder 40)
    - Old II Rural, 2004 Dec (Box 148, Folder 41)
    - Survey, 2005 Aug 3 (Box 148, Folder 42)
    - Constituent Services, 2005 Aug 9 (Box 148, Folder 43)
    - Survey-Rural Counties, 2005 Oct 6 (Box 148, Folder 44)
    - Veterans, 2005 Nov 18 (Box 148, Folder 45)
    - Energy, 2005 Nov 29 (Box 148, Folder 46)
    - Bosque County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 47)
    - Brazos County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 48)
    - Constituent Services, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 49)
    - Grimes County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 50)
    - Hill County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 51)
    - Hood County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 52)
    - Johnson County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 53)
    - Madison County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 54)
    - McLennan County, 2006 Aug (Box 148, Folder 55)
    - Veterans, 2007 June (Box 148, Folder 56)
    - Energy, 2008 July 28 (Box 148, Folder 57)
  - Newsletters, 1999-2002; 3
    - “Central Texas People, Projects and Programs Top Priority in 2000”, 2000 Aug (Box 148, Folder 58)
    - “A Message from Chet Edwards”, c. 2001-2002 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - “News from Chet Edwards”, 1999 June (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - “Special Report on the High Cost of Prescription Drugs”, 2000 Aug (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, 1991-2007; 4
    - Agriculture, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Defense, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Education, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Fort Hood, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Grant Awards, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Gun Control, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Hill County, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Homes, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - House Banking, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Internships, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Redistricting, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Schedules, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Seniors, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Service Academy Applications, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Town Hall, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Trade, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Veterans, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Water Quality, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Agriculture, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Branch Davidian Siege, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Consumer Fraud, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - Defense, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - Flooding, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 28)
    - Fort Hood, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - House Banking, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - Internships, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Small Business, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Trade, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 33)
    - Branch Davidian, 1993 (Box 149, Folder 34)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 35)
    - Business, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 36)
    - Defense, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 37)
    - Education, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 38)
    - Edwards’ Family, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 39)
    - Endangered Species, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 40)
    - Flag Amendment, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 41)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 42)
    - Fort Hood, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 43)
    - Government Shutdown, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 44)
    - Grant Awards, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 45)
    - Healthcare, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 46)
    - Lake Program, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 47)
    - Schedules, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 48)
    - Seniors, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 49)
    - Service Academy Applications, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 50)
    - Transportation, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 51)
    - Veterans, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 52)
    - Agriculture, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 53)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 54)
    - Defense, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 55)
    - Education, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 56)
    - Fort Hood, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 57)
    - Government Shutdown, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 58)
    - Grant Awards, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 59)
    - Lakes, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 60)
    - Members of Congress-Terrorism Controversy, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 61)
    - Schedules, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 62)
    - Telephone Co-Op, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 63)
    - Veterans, 1996 (Box 149, Folder 64)
    - Defense, 2001 (Box 149, Folder 65)
    - Homeland Security, 2001 (Box 149, Folder 66)
    - Agriculture, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Armed Forces, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Awards, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Bio Terrorism Bill, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Bosque County, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Financial Reform, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Cooperate Overwrite, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Crowded VFO Event, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - District Projects, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Drought Relief, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Drug Prevention, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Economy, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Education, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Fort Hood, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Hamilton County, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Homes, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Houses of Worship Bill, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Infrastructure, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Iraq, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Mammoth Site, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - McGregor, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Mendez, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - SBA Disaster Loan, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Small Business, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - Student Loans, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - Tax, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Terrorism, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 30)
    - Transportation, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 31)
    - Veterans, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 32)
    - Water Appropriations, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 33)
    - Abortion, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 34)
    - Agendas, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 35)
    - Agriculture, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 36)
    - Appropriations, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 37)
    - Armed Forces, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 38)
    - Awards, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 39)
    - Bell/Coryell County, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 40)
    - Bosque River, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 41)
    - Budget, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 42)
    - Campaign, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 43)
    - China Plane Lands, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 44)
    - Committee Appointments, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 45)
    - Committee Assignment, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 46)
    - Copperas Cove, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 47)
    - Defense, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 48)
    - District, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 49)
    - Education, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 50)
    - Events, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 51)
    - Flood Control, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 52)
    - Fort Hood, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 53)
    - Georgetown Office, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 54)
    - Hamilton, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 55)
    - Health, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 56)
    - Hunting, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 57)
    - Iraq, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 58)
    - McLennan County, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 59)
    - Military Construction, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 60)
    - Mills County, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 61)
    - Press Conference, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 62)
    - Redistricting, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 63)
    - Robert Gray Air Field, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 64)
    - Science/Technology, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 65)
    - Tax, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 66)
    - Temple, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 67)
    - Terrorism, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 68)
    - Transportation, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 69)
    - Unemployment, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 70)
    - Veterans, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 71)
    - Waco, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 72)
    - Williamson County, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 73)
    - Agriculture, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture/Rural Development Funding, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Airport Park, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Armed Forces, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Awards, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Bosque County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Brazos County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Campaign, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Central Texas, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Cinco de Mayo, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Communication, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Coryell/Bell County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Defense, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Disaster Assistance, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Education, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Events, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Firefighters, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Fort Hood, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Goldthwaite, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Granbury, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Grimes County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 22)
    - Gun Control, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 23)
    - Ham Creek Park, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 24)
    - Hamilton County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - Health, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 26)
    - Hill County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 27)
    - Homeland Security, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 28)
    - Iraq, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 29)
    - Labor, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 30)
    - McLennan Community College, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 31)
    - McLennan County, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 32)
    - Quinn Campus, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 33)
    - Redistricting, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 34)
    - September 11, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 35)
    - Social Security, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 36)
    - Tax, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 37)
    - Texas A&M, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 38)
    - Temple College, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 39)
    - Transportation, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 40)
    - Veterans, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 41)
    - Waco, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 42)
    - Water Quality, 2004 (Box 151, Folder 43)
    - Agriculture, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 44)
    - Armed Forces, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 45)
    - Awards, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 46)
    - Bankruptcy, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 47)
    - Baylor University, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 48)
    - Bell/Coryell Count, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 49)
    - Black History Month, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 50)
    - Brazos County, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 51)
    - Brazos Valley, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 52)
    - Bryan, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 53)
    - Bryan/College Station, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 54)
    - Budget, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 55)
    - Burleson, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 56)
    - Clifton, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 57)
    - College Station, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 58)
    - Committee Appointments, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 59)
    - Communication, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 60)
    - Congressman Jake Pickle, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 61)
    - Crime, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 62)
    - Defense, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 63)
    - Disaster Assistance, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 64)
    - Dove Hunt, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 65)
    - Education, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 66)
    - Energy, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 67)
    - Event, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 68)
    - Fort Hood, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 69)
    - Glen Rose, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 70)
    - Granbury, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 71)
    - Grimes County, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Groesbeck, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Gun Control, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Ham Creek Park, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Health, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Hill County, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Hillsboro, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Homeland Security, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Hood County, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Interior, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Iraq, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 11)